ALVARO CONDORI

+54 387 5329377 | condorialvaro95@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/alvarocondori1995/

Overview

I am a Web developer with experience in the use of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MEAN Stack, and MERN Stack. I have a great capacity for analyzing code and leading projects. I love to code and create useful and meaningful solutions for the problems I run into. I am a self-taught proactive person, I love to learn about programming, coding, content creation, and any new tool that helps me be more efficient

Education

Brigham Young University - Idaho

September 2022 - Present

Idaho

WEB DEVELOPMENT - Certificate

Master web development basics: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and server-side scripting (PHP)

Learn data manipulation, database management (SQL and NoSQL), and problem-solving through coding

Brigham Young University - Idaho

September 2021 - June 2022

WEB AND COMPUTER PROGRAMMING - Certificate

Idaho

Create programs for diverse tasks

Design visually appealing and efficient websites

Develop dynamic webpages adhering to industry standards. Learn and implement new technologies in programming

Experience

Self Employed January 2023 - Present

Full-Stack Developer Argentina - Remote

- Performed basic web design for local businesses, developing responsive and dynamic websites
- Maintained web sites created, to ensure long-term client satisfaction
- Developed 20+ functional, maintainable sites, using MEAN and MERN technologies

Riftbox Brands January 2023 - March 2024

Amazon Ops

Utah, USA - Remote

- Conducted listing maintenance and updates constantly, improving account's overall performance to be over 99% compliance
- Built over 15 new family variations and product listings, monitoring compliance to Amazon's policy
- Performed several reports to keep track of sales and overall account status, doing at least 2 audits a week a keeping track of cases
- Monitored Amazon Account health and performance notifications, being able to fix stranded inventory to be always at 0%

Berlitz Corporation

August 2022 - December 2022

English Teacher

Argentina - Remote

• Planned classes to teach individuals and groups, adapting to personal needs and expectations for each class, for ever 50 students and groups

Alianza America January 2022 - July 2022

English Teacher

Argentina - Remote

• Planned classes to teach individuals and groups, adapting to personal needs and expectations for each class, for ever 50 students and groups

Brazil Fortaleza Mission May 2018 - October 2019

Executive Secretary

Ceará, Brazil - OnSite

- Managed and maintained all records records, being able to go from over 25 non registered events to 0
- Managed inventory used from entire organization, ensuring a permanent supply of mandatory items weekly
- Executed daily, weekly and monthly reports, improving overall success

Skills

Word package
Data Entry
Intermediate Accounting
Fluent English and Portuguese
Project Management